Brandon Robertson

Full Stack Developer

The Basin, Victoria brandonrobertson23@gmail.com

Bio

Brandon has a strong customer focus which has been developed through his previous roles. Outside of the workplace he will proactively use his time to write/produce music and relax while enjoying the latest video games. His interest in sales, and gaming have made him a strong team player while also creating a problem solving maniac and combining that with his passion for tech and programming make him a strong developer for any team.

Employment History

Junior Web Developer - Casual at Sport Tech Mar 2021 — Present Sydney, NSW Daily

Reception / Manager Duties at Spoilt Rotten Jul 2014 — Dec 2019 Lilyfield, NSW Dogs

Picking / Packing / Sales / Warehouse Work Feb 2016 — Mar 2017 Five Dock, NSW at Car Care Products

Customer Service / Sales at Contact Centres Jan 2013 — Dec 2013 Sydney, NSW Australia

Internships

Junior Web Developer at Sport Tech Daily Feb 2021 — Mar 2021

Education

Sydney, NSW

Coder Academy Mar 2020 — Jan 2021

Melbourne, VIC Diploma of Information Technology

TAFE Nov 2011 — Oct 2012

Ultimo, NSW Music Industry

Concord High School Jan 2009 — Dec 2012 Concord, NSW Higher School Certificate

References

Sport Tech Daily

Nakul Pednekar - Available Upon Request

Spoilt Rotten Dogs

Mario Pekar - Available Upon Request

Details

The Basin, Victoria 0431 301 705

Skills

JavaScript / MERN Stack

Ruby / Ruby on Rails

HTML5, CSS3 & SASS

Test-Driven Development

Version Control (via

GitHub)

Agile Methodologies

Hobbies

Video Games, Writing and Producing Music, Learning new Instruments and Cooking

Links

Portfolio:

https://brandonrobertson.dev

GitHub & LinkedIn:

brandon-robertson-dev